<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyAssociation</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Guide</string>
    <string name="b1">E-Mail</string>
    <string name="b2">Contact</string>
    <string name="b3">Directory</string>
    <string name="b4">Weather</string>
    <string name="b5">Calendar</string>
    <string name="b6">Budget</string>
    <string name="b7">Documents</string>
    <string name="b8">Message Board</string>
    <string name="b9">My Info</string>
    <string name="b10">Push History</string>
    <string name="b11">Service Providers</string>
    <string name="b12">Change/Add Association</string>
    <string name="b13">Pet Directory</string>
    <string name="b14">Guest Directory</string>
    <string name="b15">Auto Directory</string>
    <string name="b16">Tools</string>
    <string name="b17">Push/Email</string>
    <string name="b18">Maint. Items</string>

    <string name="guide_text">My Association\n
Custom Mobile Application\n
\nWelcome to the My Association Custom Mobile Application!\n\n  The My Association Mobile App is designed to enable private
        communication between you, other members
        and the Association, quick access to information about Association events, and the ability to receive emails and push
        notifications regarding current issues for the Association.  You can send pre-formatted emails to the Association to ask
        questions and RSVP for events.  Through the Association directory you can communication with other Association Members.
New Features in Release Version 4.0
Added a feature to allow the Administrator to prescreen member posted messages and comments to the message board.  This is only
        used when member posting privileges have been authorized by the Association.\n\n
Registering for the My Association App\n\n
The first time you access the app, you will be asked to enter a passcode sent to you by the Association Administrator.  To register,
        enter the passcode if accepted you will be sent to your personal information page.  Enter your personal information for both
        of your “Two Addresses”, (Note: you must enter a First and Last Name for the registration to complete failure to do this and
        the app will not function).  (Note: This is your information for this device, not family information.)  This is the information
        that will be seen by other Association members when they access your listing in the directory. After you have entered the information,
        press the Save button.
\n\nAssociation Calendar\n\n
The Association Calendar function is a list of the currently published events scheduled for your Association.  When you access the events,
        you have the ability to add that event to your default calendar on your device and/or to respond to the Association for that event
        with a custom email by just pressing the button for either Respond to Association or Add to Calendar.
\n\nContact Us\n\n
The Contact Us function has preloaded the Association phone numbers used to contact the different organizations relevant to your Association.
\n\nDirectory\n\n
This function gives you access to the Association Membership Directory.  You can search for a member by depressing the search bar and then
        select the search method, Name or Address and then entering part of the member’s name or address.  When you have found the member,
        just depress the member’s cell and the directory listing will appear.  If you want to call the member depress the phone number you
        wish to call.  To send an email to the member just depress the email address and a blank email will be created for you to complete.
        When you have finished completing the email just depress the “Send” button.  When you are finished just depress the “Done” button or
        the Menu option on the bottom of the screen.
\n\nWeather\n\n
The Weather function provides you the current weather conditions at your Association Location, with weather condition, temperature, and wind
        speed and direction.  It also provides you with the forecast for the day with the weather condition, high and low temperatures,
        and forecasted wind speed and direction.
\n\nGuide\n\n
The Guide provides the complete documentation on all of the functions contained in the app.
\n\nBudget\n\n
The Budget provides the latest budget and/or expenses for the Association.  You can zoom the document and reposition using normal gestures
        for the device. You should have WiFi access for this to load, since these files reside in the cloud server.
\n\nDocuments\n\n
The Documents provides the “ByLaws”, “Rules” and “Current Minutes” and an additional three documents selected by the association for Members
        of the Association to view.  You can zoom the document and reposition using normal gestures
        for the device.  You should have WiFi access for this to load, since these files reside in the cloud server.
\n\nPush History\n\n
The Push History provides the member access to the last 60 days worth of push notices.  The notices are automatically removed after 60 days.
\n\nService Providers\n\n
This is member feature if activated by the Association Administrator to allow members to pass on information on service providers that they
        have used and recommend to other members of the association.  This feature allows you to add new Service Categories and then add providers
        to that category.  Members also have the ability to add notes or comments to a providers listing for additional information.
\n\nChg/Add Assoc\n\n
The Chg/Add Assoc provides the member the ability to be a member of multiple associations using the MyAssociation App.  To join a new association
        depress the “+” plus button on the upper right of the screen and then enter the passcode for your new association.  To change the current
        association, just depress the association you wish to change to and the app will be reconfigured for that association.  Note: you will not
        receive push notifications for the association that is not your current association.
\n\nMyInfo\n\n
The MyInfo provides you access to update your personal information for the Association’s Directory. When you update and “Save” this information
        is updated for all members to view.  This section also contains the “Buttons” to update your Pet, Automobile and Guest Information, if this
        information was requested by your Association Administrator.
\n\nMessage Board\n\n
The Message Board provides you access to messages posted by other members or the Administrator and the ability to respond to that message directly
        to the posting party. Only the posting party and Association Administrator can delete a post by swiping the cell from right to left.
        To add a post just depress the “+” button on the upper right (This is only an option for members if approved by the Administrator) and you
        will have displayed an “Add Message” screen that you can enter your post in the text box.  When you are finished just depress the “Save”
        button and your post will be added to the Message Board.  A red circle on the upper right of the Message Board Button indicates that new
        messages are available.  When a new message is created a “Push Notification” is sent to all members notifying them that a new message
        was created.  You also have the ability to post a “Comment” on a message by depressing the “Comment” button.  This will take you to the
        input comment screen where you will enter your comment and then depress the “Save” button to post the comment or depress “Cancel” and the
        comment will be discarded. If authorized by the Association, all member posted messages and comments will be prescreened by the association
        prior to being posted to the message board.
\n\nMaintenance Items\n\n
The Maint. Items, provides the members the ability to post maintenance requests with the Association Administrator.  There is also the ability
        to post a comment on the request.  This option is an Association requested option, so not all associations will have this ability.
\n\nPet Directory\n\n
The Pet Directory, provides the members the ability to view the pets that the Association Owners have entered into the database.  This option is
        an Association requested option, so not all associations will have this ability.
\n\nAuto Directory\n\n
The Auto Directory, provides the members the ability to view the automobiles that the Association Owners have entered into the database.
        This option is an Association requested option, so not all associations will have this ability
</string>


</resources>
